degify.com 2014-06-25

# Disc Makers Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to Disc Makers. Here is how Disc Makers collects, uses, and safeguards the personal information you provide on our Web site:

Information collection

When you browse Disc Makers' Web site, we do not collect personal information, including your email address. We do log the Internet address of your computer - your IP address - to give us an idea of which parts of our Web site you visit and how long you spend there. This type of information helps us to continually develop our Web site to best meet your needs. We do not link your IP address to anything personally identifiable, and unless you register on our site, we do not know your personal identity.

Like many other Web sites, Disc Makers' Web site may use a standard technology called an "Internet cookie." Internet cookies are small files that may be placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes:

1) to estimate our audience size by determining repeat usage of the Web site; and 

2) to measure certain traffic patterns for use as a research tool to understand how our users' habits are similar or different from one another. We use these records help us to improve our Web site.   
Please also be aware that Web sites that have links to our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites are not covered in this privacy statement. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those Web sites you visit. 

Information use

Once you register on our site, Disc Makers will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others without your consent. If you provide us with your email or postal address on our online registration forms, we ask you if we can use it to send you updates on the latest Disc Makers products, special promotions, and newsletters. At no time will we share your email address with third parties. We also ask if you want us to share your personal information with other companies that offer related services. If you do not want us or other companies to contact you, you can choose to "opt out" and Disc Makers will not send you the information you have declined to receive. 

Disc Makers does research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us during your use of the Disc Makers Web site. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. Disc Makers may share this aggregated data with others. 

Declining Email offers

Disc Makers provides customers with an easy means to decline to receive email offers and newsletters. Although most customers tell us they appreciate receiving our newsletters and notice of special offers, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers from us by emailing us at [privacy@discmakers.com.](mailto:privacy@discmakers.com) All email offers and newsletters that you receive from Disc Makers will tell you how to decline further emails. 

Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, including credit card numbers entered on the /shop page, we have physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information you provide us online. To protect your information once your transaction is complete, Disc Makers stores your information on an off-line server stored securely behind our firewall. There is no external access to this information and its internal access is strictly monitored. 

Disc Makers takes appropriate steps to communicate our privacy policy and guidelines to all employees. 

Disc Makers' privacy policy is subject to change at any time. Disc Makers will provide notice 30 days prior to implementing any major changes to our privacy policy. 

If you have any question specific to privacy, please contact us at [privacy@discmakers.com.](mailto:privacy@discmakers.com)

Backstage Emails 

All Backstage deals, discounts, and giveaways are provided at the sole discretion of the advertising partner. Disc Makers, and its parent company, AVL Digital Group, is not responsible for fulfillment of any products, services, or advertised offers provided by the advertising partners. All customer service inquiries will be handled by the advertising partner. All Backstage offers are valid for a period of 7 days, and are advertised as such.
